thegoodtrade.com 2018-06-25

# Privacy Policy

Welcome to the website of The Good Trade (“TGT,” “we,” “us,” or “our”). TGT is committed to protecting its users’ privacy. Our Privacy Policy (“Policy”) is designed to help you understand how we collect, use and safeguard the information you provide to us, and to assist you in making informed decisions when using our Service.

This Policy applies to your use of <http://www.thegoodtrade.com/> (the “Site”) and any other related webpages, services, applications, or functionalities. By visiting, uploading, or otherwise interacting with the Site you are subject to this Policy. If any material changes are made to this Privacy Policy, we will notify you by posting the revised Privacy Policy on the Website or notifying you through the Website. ANY ACCESS TO OR USE OF THE WEBSITE BY YOU AFTER THE CHANGES GO INTO EFFECT SHALL CONSTITUTE AND BE DEEMED YOUR AGREEMENT TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY. Accordingly, we encourage you to periodically review this Privacy Policy and the Website in order to keep apprised of our current privacy practices. If you do not agree to our privacy practices as detailed here, please do not use this Website.

Please read this policy carefully, especially before providing personal information or submissions to us.

     **1.** **     Information We Collect**
    _Personally identifiable information_

Personally identifiable information (“PII”) is any information that can be used to identify you, such as your first and last name, your email address, your physical address, phone number, etc.

We collect whatever personal data about you that you choose to give us, such as contact email addresses and profile information. If you give us an email address, we might send you promotional messages once in a while; we’ll try to make them engaging and interesting but of course you’ll be able to opt out at any time using the _unsubscribe_ link in the email.

 _Aggregate information (non-personally identifiable information)_

TGT may, from time to time, automatically collect aggregate information about our visitors to our advertisers, sponsors, promotional partners and affiliates. This aggregate information includes, but is not limited to, IP addresses connecting to our site, how many persons visited a particular page or activity, dates and times of image uploads, device characteristics, operating system, browser type, type of connection, page and image viewing statistics, and incoming and outgoing links.  

Like most websites, we use log files to store this information. None of this automatically collected technical information is associated with any identified person at the time it is collected, but it could be associated with you under two circumstances: First, if you choose to give us personal data about you as described above, the technical information we collect that would otherwise be anonymous could instead be logged as coming from you. Second, if we are required to disclose our server logs as a result of a subpoena or other legal process, some third party such as your internet provider could match our anonymous technical information with you, using information beyond what is found on our servers.

 _Mmm, Cookies_

TGT may use cookies, web beacons, pixel tags, or other anonymous tracking information to improve our server's interaction with your computer, and we may partner with third party advertisers who may (themselves or through their partners) place or recognize a unique cookie on your browser. These cookies enable more customized ads, content, or services to be provided to you. To trigger these cookies, we may pass an encrypted or "hashed" (non-human readable) identifier corresponding to your email address to a Web advertising partner, who may place a cookie on your computer. No personally identifiable information is on, or is connected to, these cookies. Although our servers currently don't respond to "do-not-track" requests (see below), you can block these cookies in other ways, for example by searching “[your browser] + disable cookies.”

     **2.** **     ****Information Use & Disclosure**

TGT will never share, sell, lease, or rent PII to unaffiliated third parties, except in the following circumstances:

a)    If we have a good faith belief that we must disclose such information for legal reasons, such as to enforce our Terms of Service, protect or assert the rights, property interests, or personal safety of TGT (including its employees, directors, suppliers, distributors, service providers, users of the Website or others), or if we are otherwise required to disclose such information by law. We will disclose information only to the extent necessary to comply with the purpose of the request.

b)   We may share aggregate, anonymous or summary information regarding our customers and their behaviors with partners, advertisers or other third parties. This data is not personal information and so will not identify you personally. We may share information with companies that provide support services to us, such as a printer, mailing house, fulfillment-company, credit card processor, email service provider or web host, amongst others. These parties may need personal information about you in order to perform their functions. However, these parties may not use any personal information we share with them about you for any other purpose other than in connection with performing supporting functions for us.

     **3.** **     ****Protecting Your Information**

TGT has implemented certain physical, administrative, and technical security measures to protect against the loss, misuse, or alteration of the information you provide. However, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. Therefore, TGT cannot warrant that your information will be absolutely secure when it is transit. Any transmission of data is at your own risk. You should take safety precautions to prevent unauthorized access to your information such as by limiting access to your computer or mobile device.

     **4.** **     ****Do Not Track**

Do Not Track (“DNT”) is a preference you can set in your browser to let websites you visit know that you do not want them collecting certain information about you. TGT does not currently respond to, or honor, Do Not Track signals or requests from your browser.

     **5.** **     ****Your Rights Regarding The Use Of Your Personal Information.**

You have the right at any time to prevent us from contacting you for marketing purposes.  If and when we send a promotional communication to a user, the user can opt out of further promotional communications by following the unsubscribe instructions provided in each promotional e-mail. Please note that notwithstanding the promotional preferences you indicate by unsubscribing or opting out in some other fashion, we may continue to send you administrative emails including, for example, periodic updates to our Privacy Policy.

     **6.** **     ****Creating an account**

( _The Good Trade does not currently offer users the ability to create accounts on our site. However, if and when this feature is enabled in the future, the following terms will apply._ )

In order to access a profile and post comments on TGT you must first create an account with a username and password. The registration system requires that a valid email address be used to confirm the account. You should choose a username that _does not_  include your last name and _does not_  specify your city or your address. The Good Trade asks that you use your first name only, or an alias, for your display name. This is to safeguard your privacy and protection.

TGT accounts are backed up regularly. If a user changes the information on his or her account, TGT’s stored data backups may include the user’s original information. If you email anyone at TGT, a record of the addresses and correspondence will continue to exist. We save this information so that we can respond to you and have a record of that correspondence.

     **7.** **     ****California Online Privacy Protection Act**

CalOPPA requires all commercial websites and online services accessible by California residences to conspicuously post a privacy policy. Per CalOPPA, we agree to the following:

·      Users can visit our site anonymously.

·      Users will be notified of any privacy policy changes on our Privacy Policy Page.

·      Users are able to change their personal information by emailing us directly at info@EMAIL.com.

     **8.** **     ****Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA)**

TGT does not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under the age of thirteen (13). If you are under the age of thirteen (13) you should not provide us with any personally identifiable information. If we learn that we have collected any information or content from anyone under the age of 13, we will delete that information immediately.

     **9.** **     ****Links to Other Websites**

TGT may, from time to time, contain links to other sites. However, we are not responsible for the privacy practices employed by those sites, or the information or content they contain. We encourage our users to be aware of this fact when they leave www.thegoodtrade.com, and to read the privacy statements of any website that collects personally identifiable information. This Privacy Policy applies only to information collected by TGT through our site and does not apply to any third-party websites linked.

     **10.** ******Anti-SPAM Policy**

TGT is 100% opposed to unsolicited commercial email ("spam"). We do not have any desire to send unsolicited marketing emails to anyone without permission and we do not sell or provide user email addresses to any unauthorized third party in violation of this Policy. All of our newsletters and other general email marketing communications also include an "unsubscribe" opt-out link that you may use to tell us to stop sending you marketing emails.

     **11.** ******What if The Good Trade is sold or closes up shop?**

In the event of a change in control resulting from, for example, a sale to, or merger with, another entity, or in the event of a sale of assets or a bankruptcy, TGT reserves the right to transfer your personal information to the new party in control, or the party acquiring assets. We will only do so if the party we transfer the information to agrees that they will abide by our Privacy Policy for as long as they hold the information, and that they will not transfer the information to any other party who will not abide by our Privacy Policy.

     **12.** ******  Sharing of Information with Partners**

As stated above, we may collect and provide aggregate information about our visitors to our advertisers, sponsors, promotional partners, and affiliates.

We use third-party advertising companies to deliver online advertising. These companies facilitate the delivery of ads, conduct market research, and use cookies for record-keeping purposes. These cookies sometimes enable the companies to serve you ads tailored to things you have shown an interest in based on your prior web activity. This is generally known as behavioral advertising. For example, this means that if you frequently read movie reviews online, it is possible that you might see ads on other websites relating to upcoming movies. Online advertising companies generally conduct this activity in an anonymous format, with online information not combined with information that would allow for your identification.

The third-party companies that will be serving advertisements on TGT may include DoubleClick, Google and Blue Kai. If you would like more information about the collection, use and disclosure practices of these companies, and/or your options for not having this information used by these companies, click on the company names above and follow the links to the company websites.

     **13.** ******Changes to our Privacy Policy**

 ** ** We may periodically modify, alter, or update this Policy. We will alert users to any material changes to this policy by posting the revised information here. We encourage you to review our Privacy Policy on a regular basis to stay informed about how we are protecting the personal information we collect. Your continued use of TGT’s website constitutes your agreement to this Privacy Policy and any future updates.

     **14.** ******Contact Information**

 ** ** Email: hello@thegoodtrade.com

Last Updated: _3/6/16_
